<resources>
    <string name="app_name">In-Sync</string>
    <string name="toast_message_screenshot_success">huuh</string>
    <string name="toast_message_screenshot">huuhhuhu</string>
    <string name="settings_message">huhuhuuhhuhuuhuhhu</string>
    <string name="recording">ghjwejkhggrjkghgsfajkghlgrhjklaljkghgfdsa</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service">The accessibility service permisstion allows InSync to perform gestures on your device screen. \n\n
        This permission is required inorder to execute the clicks and swipes you will create in your automations scenerios \n\n
        InSync commits we would not gain your private information
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="insync_description_1">
        Automate, optimize, and elevate your Android experience with InSync. Whether you are
        <b><font color="#18181B">refining app tests or streamlining daily tasks</font></b>,
        InSync adapts to your needs—bringing seamless automation right to your fingertips.
    </string>
    <string name="insync_description_2">
        InSync is an advanced automation tool designed for Android applications, enabling you to create, customize, and execute automation scripts with ease.
    </string>
    <string name="insync_description_3">
        By leveraging a powerful web-based interface and an intuitive Android client, InSync allows developers and testers to automate complex scenarios without relying on traditional ADB methods.
    </string>
    <string name="card_header_2">No ADB Required</string>
    <string name="card_header_1">Visual Script Customization</string>
    <string name="card_header_3">Real-time Execution</string>
    <string name="card_content_1">Our web service offers a user-friendly platform to visually create and customize automation scripts, making the process faster and more accessible.</string>
    <string name="card_content_2">Unlike traditional tools, InSync uses Android\'s accessibility services, eliminating the need for complex ADB setups.</string>
    <string name="card_content_3">Experience seamless script execution directly on your Android device, with real-time logs to monitor every action.</string>
    <string name="startDesc">Continue exploring, tweaking, and perfecting your scripts to streamline your productivity.</string>
    <string name="wt_text_1">Create Your Script</string>
    <string name="wt_text_2">Customize and Personalize</string>
    <string name="wt_text_3">Precise Log History</string>
    <string name="wt_desc_1">Use our intuitive script editor to design the sequence of actions that match your workflow. Whether its a simple task or a complex series of operation.</string>
    <string name="wt_desc_2">Adjust parameters, set conditions, and loop actions to create a script that is tailored to your exact needs. The possibilities are endless.</string>
    <string name="wt_desc_3">Stay informed with detailed and precise logs. Every action, every change, and every task performed by InSync is logged meticulously, so you always know what’s happening behind the scenes.</string>
</resources>